Makitimelo Joel Lekala

E-mail: makitimelolekala@gmail.com Phone: 0670482033

Address: 351 6th Road, Montana, Pretoria North, Gauteng, 0182

Summary

Personally, I am a quick study and problem solver. I work well on tasks either individually or as part of a team. I would like appreciate being considered for the above job posting and advance my skills to benefit not only myself, but the organization as well. Completed my Software Development Diploma at the Tshwane University of Technology specializing in SQL, .NET OOP and systems design and implementation. Throughout my working journey i have acquired valuable skills that compliments my hard working spirit and determination towards the job, from backend competencies to those of frontend. Thank you for your consideration.

Work experience

Tsogo Sun

IT Development Intern

Job responsibilities

April 2019 — March 2020

- System Development
- · Developing databases and support them
- · Back-end application development
- · Front-end application development
- · Testing systems
- Developing prototypes
- · Presenting prototypes to users
- · Creating and managing project plans
- Creating technical specification documents
- Database design
- Software testing
- · Creating user manuals
- · Implementing systems into live environment
- · Software support
- Managing project status meetings

Purple Online Media Solutions

Junior .NET Developer(Remote)

Job responsibilities:

Maintenance

Support

Software Testing

Database Design

Documentation

Back-end Development

July 2020 — June 2022

Makitimelo Joel Lekala

Front-end Development
Software Deployment
Hangfire Job monitoring
Presenting demo to client
Managing project status meetings
Analysing business requirements
Developing user manuals

Technologies:

C#, MVC, Vuejs, jQuery, SQL

ITIAM

Junior .NET Developer(Remote)

Job responsibilities:

Maintenance

Support

Software Testing

Database Design

Documentation

Back-end Development

Front-end Development

Software Deployment

Hangfire Job monitoring

Presenting demo to client

Managing project status meetings

Analysing business requirements

Developing user manuals

Technologies:

C#, MVC, Vuejs, jQuery, SQL, Adonisjs, Hangfire

MoData

Junior .NET Developer(Remote)

Job responsibilities:

Maintenance

Support

Software Testing

Database Design

Documentation

Back-end Development

Front-end Development

Software Deployment

Hangfire Job monitoring

Presenting demo to client

Managing project status meetings

Analysing business requirements

Developing user manuals

Technologies:

C#, MVC, Vuejs, jQuery, SQL

Boxfusion

Mid-Level Developer

August 2020 — March 2022

July 2020 — March 2022

July 2022 — Present

Makitimelo loel Lekala

Job responsibilities:

Maintenance Support

Software Testing

Back-end Development

Technologies:

C#, MVVM, Knockoutjs, Vuejs, jQuery, SQL, Dev0ps

Qualifications

NOV 2014 - NATIONAL SENIOR CERTIFICATE

Subjects and Grades

Sepedi Home Language English First Additional Language Mathematics Life Orientation Geography Life Sciences

762- Microsoft Developing SQL Databases

Date Completed: December 11, 2020

Credential ID: 990503631

Education

Physical Sciences

NATIONAL DIPLOMA SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT (EXTENDED)

JANUARY 2015 — DECEMBER 2018

TSHWANE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

JAN - 2015 - NATIONAL DIPLOMA IT(SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT)

Subjects:

Foundation Academic and Language Skills

Foundation ICT Mathematical Skills

Foundation Information & Software development Skills

Foundation Presentation and Reporting Skills

Computing Fundamentals IA

Computing Systems IA

Development Software IA

Computing Skills IA

Computing Fundamentals IB

Computing Systems IB

Development Software IB

Computing Skills IB

Development Software IIA

Information Systems IIA

System Software IIA

Technical Programming I

Development Software IIB

Information Systems IIB

Makitimelo Joel Lekala 3

System Software IIB
Technical Programming II
Information Systems IIIA
Information Systems IIIB
Development Software IIIB
Development Software IIIA
Industry Exposure IIIA
Industry Exposure IIIB

Interests

Music, Reading, Coding

References

Maanda Matshili Relationship: Mentor Contact: 084 344 0602

Personal Skills and Competencies

- jQuery
- Bootstrap4
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Ajax
- MS SQL
- Angular
- System Analysis and Design
- Entity Framework6
- Microsoft Web Stack (MVC, C#, Razor, IIS, ASP.Net)
- .NET Core
- Smartsheet Project Management
- JSON
- JavaScript
- Postman
- Content Management System(Wordpress)
- Hangfire
- Microsoft SQL Server
- Vue.js
- Git
- Nodejs
- mySQL
- Adonisjs

Personal Information

Race: Black

Languages: Sepedi, Sesotho, English

Makitimelo Joel Lekala 4